JAMES ANDEREGG

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Golden, Co 80401

Process-driven, self-learner with the patience and curiosity to solve any problem. 4+ years of experience in Front-end Development, Back-end Development and Data Science studies with the willingness to learn and master any skill to solve a problem.

Phone: (303)517-7750
Email: jamesanderegg@jamesandereg.com
Website: https://www.jamesanderegg.com/
linkedin.com/in/james-anderegg
github.com/james-anderegg

KEY SKILLS

Front End

- ReactJS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, D3
- CSS3, ES6, GRAPHQL, Apollo, Axios
- HTML5, JSON, RESTful API

Backend

- Python, Flask
- Node.js, GitHub, Github-Pages
- Authorization, Authentication

Databases

- MySQL, NoSQL, SQLite, SSMS, SSRS, SSIS
- MongoDB, AWS Dynamo DB
- ORM, Snapshot Replication, Migration

Data Science

- Python, Pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib, Plotly
- Power Bi, Tableau
- TensorFlow, Keras

WORK HISTORY

DataFluent, LLC 05/01/2018 – Present

CEO – FREELANCE WORK Denver, CO

- Perform a database duplication and snapshot queries with SSMS to improve database integrity and provide a safe environment for data to be cleaned.
- Connect multiple data sources to Power Bi using API connections and Python scripts.
- Prepare, maintain, design and build dashboards for KPI reports in Power Bi and create a report hierarchy.
- Build out data flows between Zoom, Dropbox and GitHub and GitHub-Pages.
- Develop and design static websites for incredibly fast page loads and asset optimization.

Art Installation Services 2009 – 2019

CO - CEO Denver, CO

- Systems manager, Client scheduling, Employee management
- Built and maintained a website, blog and social media presence with a year over year increased traffic and sales.
- Professional communication, learning to solve problems and build morale when plans change.

EDUCATION

The University of Denver

12/01/2018 - 05/31/2019

Full-Stack Data Analyst Certification

Denver, CO

The University of Northern Colorado

08/01/2006 - 05/31/2009

• Fine Arts, emphasizing in Painting and Web Graphics

Denver, CO